<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Products on Avokado Project</title>
    <link>https://avokadoproject.github.io/products/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Products on Avokado Project</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://avokadoproject.github.io/products/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Avito Android Infrastructure</title>
      <link>https://avokadoproject.github.io/products/avito-android-infra/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://avokadoproject.github.io/products/avito-android-infra/</guid>
      <description>Our engineers working for Avito have made available in open source the entire infrastructure of the company&amp;rsquo;s Android apps.
There you can find:
 Test framework for UI tests Test runner CI/CD plugins for Android Studio/IntelliJ IDEA Plugin for Android Studio/IntelliJ IDEA for environment checks IDE speed up tips and performance benchmarks And much more.  The project comes complete with public documentation, which is actively expanded and updated.
Project contributors are available in Telegram chat in both Russian and English.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kaspresso</title>
      <link>https://avokadoproject.github.io/products/kaspresso/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://avokadoproject.github.io/products/kaspresso/</guid>
      <description>Kaspresso is a UI test framework based on Espresso and UI Automator. Developed by Kaspersky. It greatly simplifies writing autotests for Android apps and offers multiple features, where the most important are:
 100% stability and reliability Faster execution of Espresso and UI Automator commands. For some commands in the latter, the speed increase is 10x Excellent test readability thanks to a readily comprehensible DSL An incredible interceptor mechanism allowing to intercept all actions and asserts in one place Clear logging Support for ADB calls Autotest writing philosophy and a DSL compliant with this philosophy Fast screenshot tool And much more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Autotests</title>
      <link>https://avokadoproject.github.io/products/autotests/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://avokadoproject.github.io/products/autotests/</guid>
      <description>Coming soon…</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>